<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>COOK/HACK</title><link href="http://blog.cookhub.me/atom.xml" rel="self"></link><link href="http://blog.cookhub.me/"></link><updated>2013-03-12T20:50:06-04:00</updated><id>http://blog.cookhub.me</id><author><name>Jimmy Chao</name><email>daizenga@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">We are betaing!</title><link>href="http://blog.cookhub.me/2013/03/12/we-are-betaing.html"/></link><updated>2013-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://blog.cookhub.me We are betaing!</id><content type="html"><![CDATA[
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Beta&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/beta.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Cookhub is betaing!!!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are releasing the beta version of Cookhub.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all the hardwork from the team!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href=&quot;https://cookhub.uservoice.com/&quot;&gt;please tell us your opinion about the site&lt;/a&gt;, only with your help that we can make cookhub better.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content></entry><entry><title type="html">Improving cooking experience</title><link>href="http://blog.cookhub.me/2013/03/11/improving-cooking-experience.html"/></link><updated>2013-03-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://blog.cookhub.me Improving cooking experience</id><content type="html"><![CDATA[
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;old recipe&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/oldrecipe.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything starts as a small idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning, it&#39;s just an small thought on the subway back from work.
I am pretty tired during the work, 
so I don&#39;t want to cook anything and concidering take some food back.
But I came up with a thought:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;How would I improve the cooking experience,&lt;br/&gt;make cooking become a more enjoyable, delightful event for family and friends?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After few months, this idea grows and become the essential question that cookhub trying to solve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Feeds&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On cookhub, we try to encourage people to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only the recipe, but any dish that people have made from cookhub or other recipe websites.
By sharing, people can feel more acomplishment on making food, also be able to
track the dish they have made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/feed.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We simplify the sharing process as simple as posting a picture on facebook and twitter.
For a dish, people don&#39;t need to write any detail ingredients and instructions. 
A few lines of how it made from is okay. User can opt-in to write a more details recipe as their wish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/make.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, people can follow their friends and interested person.
Knowing what they made and explore more different tastes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Todos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/todo.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When user saw a good recipe on cookhub, we want to add a trigger to encourage user to make it,
and publish the result to the recipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Todos, is an attempt to let user can easily track the recipes they want to make,
and brought ingredients from recipes. Make it easier to make and share on recipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Recipe&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/recipe.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are trying to redesign the recipe to make it more appeal to reader and easy to make.
Also viewable on phone and tablet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although we are still pretty far from the target, but we will working hard to improve the cookhub.
Stay tune for future update!&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content></entry></feed>